mouser.com 2002-08-03

# Mouser Electronics © 2002

|   

Mouser Electronics Inc &  
Statement of Internet Privacy

At Mouser, we are committed to protecting your privacy and to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, this statement of privacy explains data collection and the use in these situations. Please read the complete Mouser Privacy Statement. 

Collecting your Personal Information:  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are ordering e-mail newsletters, catalogs or when purchasing Mouser products. Mouser actively monitor's it's web site for errors. If an error occurs, information about your web browser may be collected in order to better assist us in correcting the problem. 

Use of your Personal Information:  
We may use your personal information for four primary purposes: 1) To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once. 2) To help you quickly find services or information on Mouser. 3) To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you. 4) To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services from Mouser. 5.) To contact you in the event we notice you received an error while using our web site in order to troubleshoot the problem and help you resolve it. 

Mouser Electronics, Inc. will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Mouser. (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Mouser and it's Web sites, and (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of others or Mouser, it's Web sites, or the public. 

Control of your Personal Information:  
When you register, or otherwise give us your personal information, Mouser will not share that information with third parties. It will only be used for the purposes stated above. 

Security of your Personal Information:  
Mouser strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for it's intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

Changes to this Statement:  
Mouser will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this Statement, Mouser will notify you by placing notice on the website. 

Contact Information  
Mouser Electronics, Inc.  
1000 N. Main Street  
Mansfield, Texas 76063  
webmaster@mouser.com  
Copyright © 2002 Mouser Electronics, Inc.  
All Rights reserved. 

This document was last updated August 28, 2001. 

| 

* * *

Copyright © 2001 Mouser Electronics, Inc. Mouser ® and Mouser Electronics ® are registered trademarks of Mouser Electronics, Inc. Other products, logos and company names mentioned herein, may be trademarks of their respected owners. Catalog files represented as .pdf files are © 2001 Mouser Electronics, Inc. and may not be reproduced.
